A Guide to the Militia Commission Papers, 1777-1858
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Militia Commissions, 1777-1858., Extent: 66.71 cu. ft. (169 boxes). (Box 3-171)
  - Subseries A. Counties, 1777-1858.
    - Shenandoah County, 1783. (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Shenandoah County, 1784. (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Shenandoah County, 1785. (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Shenandoah County, 1786. (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Shenandoah County, 1787. (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Shenandoah County, 1788. (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Shenandoah County, 1789. (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Shenandoah County, 1790. (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Shenandoah County, 1793. (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Shenandoah County, 1794. (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Shenandoah County, 1795. (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Shenandoah County, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Shenandoah County, 1797. (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Shenandoah County, 1798. (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Shenandoah County, 1799. (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Shenandoah County, 1800. (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Shenandoah County, 1801. (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Shenandoah County, 1802. (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Shenandoah County, 1803. (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - Shenandoah County, 1804. (Box 142, Folder 20)
    - Shenandoah County, 1805. (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - Shenandoah County, 1806. (Box 142, Folder 22)
    - Shenandoah County, 1807. (Box 142, Folder 23)
    - Shenandoah County, 1808. (Box 142, Folder 24)
    - Shenandoah County, 1809. (Box 142, Folder 25)
    - Shenandoah County, 1810. (Box 142, Folder 26)
    - Shenandoah County, 1811. (Box 142, Folder 27)
    - Shenandoah County, 1812. (Box 142, Folder 28)
    - Shenandoah County, 1813. (Box 142, Folder 29)
    - Shenandoah County, 1814. (Box 142, Folder 30)
    - Shenandoah County, 1815. (Box 142, Folder 31)
    - Shenandoah County, 1816. (Box 142, Folder 32)
    - Shenandoah County, 1817. (Box 142, Folder 33)
    - Shenandoah County, 1818. (Box 142, Folder 34)
    - Shenandoah County, 1819. (Box 142, Folder 35)
    - Shenandoah County, 1820. (Box 142, Folder 36)
    - Shenandoah County, 1821. (Box 142, Folder 37)
    - Shenandoah County, 1822. (Box 142, Folder 38)
    - Shenandoah County, 1823. (Box 142, Folder 39)
    - Shenandoah County, 1824. (Box 142, Folder 40)
    - Shenandoah County, 1825. (Box 142, Folder 41)
    - Shenandoah County, 1826. (Box 142, Folder 42)
    - Shenandoah County, 1827. (Box 142, Folder 43)
    - Shenandoah County, 1828. (Box 142, Folder 44)
    - Shenandoah County, 1829. (Box 142, Folder 45)
    - Shenandoah County, 1830. (Box 142, Folder 46)
    - Shenandoah County, 1831. (Box 142, Folder 47)
    - Shenandoah County, 1832. (Box 142, Folder 48)
    - Shenandoah County, 1833. (Box 142, Folder 49)
    - Shenandoah County, 1834. (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Shenandoah County, 1835. (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Shenandoah County, 1836. (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Shenandoah County, 1837. (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Shenandoah County, 1838. (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Shenandoah County, 1839. (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Shenandoah County, 1840. (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Shenandoah County, 1841. (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Shenandoah County, 1842. (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Shenandoah County, 1843. (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Shenandoah County, 1844. (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Shenandoah County, 1845. (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Shenandoah County, 1846. (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Shenandoah County, 1847. (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Shenandoah County, 1848. (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Shenandoah County, 1849. (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Shenandoah County, 1850. (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Shenandoah County, 1851. (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Shenandoah County, 1852. (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Shenandoah County, 1854. (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Shenandoah County, 1856. (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Shenandoah County, undated. (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Smyth County, 1832. (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Smyth County, 1834. (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Smyth County, 1835. (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Smyth County, 1836. (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Smyth County, 1837. (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Smyth County, 1838. (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Smyth County, 1839. (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Smyth County, 1840. (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Smyth County, 1841. (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Smyth County, 1842. (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Smyth County, 1843. (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Smyth County, 1844. (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Smyth County, 1845. (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Smyth County, 1846. (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Smyth County, 1847. (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Smyth County, 1848. (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - Smyth County, 1849. (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - Smyth County, 1850. (Box 144, Folder 18)
    - Smyth County, 1851. (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - Smyth County, 1852. (Box 144, Folder 20)
    - Smyth County, 1853. (Box 144, Folder 21)
    - Smyth County, 1854. (Box 144, Folder 22)
    - Southampton County, 1783. (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Southampton County, 1784. (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Southampton County, 1785. (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Southampton County, 1786. (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Southampton County, 1787. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Southampton County, 1788. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Southampton County, 1789. (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Southampton County, 1790. (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Southampton County, 1791. (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Southampton County, 1792. (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Southampton County, 1793. (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Southampton County, 1794. (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Southampton County, 1795. (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Southampton County, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Southampton County, 1797. (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Southampton County, 1798. (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - Southampton County, 1799. (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - Southampton County, 1800. (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - Southampton County, 1801. (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - Southampton County, 1802. (Box 145, Folder 20)
    - Southampton County, 1803. (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - Southampton County, 1804. (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - Southampton County, 1805. (Box 145, Folder 23)
    - Southampton County, 1806. (Box 145, Folder 24)
    - Southampton County, 1807. (Box 145, Folder 25)
    - Southampton County, 1808. (Box 145, Folder 26)
    - Southampton County, 1809. (Box 145, Folder 27)
    - Southampton County, 1810. (Box 145, Folder 28)
    - Southampton County, 1811. (Box 145, Folder 29)
    - Southampton County, 1812. (Box 145, Folder 30)
    - Southampton County, 1813. (Box 145, Folder 31)
    - Southampton County, 1814. (Box 145, Folder 32)
    - Southampton County, 1815. (Box 145, Folder 33)
    - Southampton County, 1816. (Box 145, Folder 34)
    - Southampton County, 1817. (Box 145, Folder 35)
    - Southampton County, 1818. (Box 145, Folder 36)
    - Southampton County, 1819. (Box 145, Folder 37)
    - Southampton County, 1820. (Box 145, Folder 38)
    - Southampton County, 1821. (Box 145, Folder 39)
    - Southampton County, 1822. (Box 145, Folder 40)
    - Southampton County, 1823. (Box 145, Folder 41)
    - Southampton County, 1824. (Box 145, Folder 42)
    - Southampton County, 1825. (Box 145, Folder 43)
    - Southampton County, 1826. (Box 145, Folder 44)
    - Southampton County, 1827. (Box 145, Folder 45)
    - Southampton County, 1828. (Box 145, Folder 46)
    - Southampton County, 1829. (Box 145, Folder 47)
    - Southampton County, 1830. (Box 145, Folder 48)
    - Southampton County, 1831. (Box 145, Folder 49)
    - Southampton County, 1832. (Box 145, Folder 50)
    - Southampton County, 1833. (Box 145, Folder 51)
    - Southampton County, 1834. (Box 145, Folder 52)
    - Southampton County, 1835. (Box 145, Folder 53)
    - Southampton County, 1836. (Box 145, Folder 54)
    - Southampton County, 1837. (Box 145, Folder 55)
    - Southampton County, 1838. (Box 145, Folder 56)
    - Southampton County, 1839. (Box 145, Folder 57)
    - Southampton County, 1840. (Box 145, Folder 58)
    - Southampton County, 1841. (Box 145, Folder 59)
    - Southampton County, 1842. (Box 145, Folder 60)
    - Southampton County, 1843. (Box 145, Folder 61)
    - Southampton County, 1844. (Box 145, Folder 62)
    - Southampton County, 1845. (Box 145, Folder 63)
    - Southampton County, 1846. (Box 145, Folder 64)
    - Southampton County, 1847. (Box 145, Folder 65)
    - Southampton County, 1848. (Box 145, Folder 66)
    - Southampton County, 1849. (Box 145, Folder 67)
    - Southampton County, 1850. (Box 145, Folder 68)
    - Southampton County, 1851. (Box 145, Folder 69)
    - Southampton County, 1852. (Box 145, Folder 70)
    - Southampton County, 1856. (Box 145, Folder 71)
    - Southampton County, undated. (Box 145, Folder 72)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1784. (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1785. (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1786. (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1787. (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1788. (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1789. (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1790. (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1791. (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1793. (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1794. (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1795. (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1797. (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1798. (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1799. (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1800. (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1801. (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1802. (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1803. (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1804. (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1805. (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1806. (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1807. (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1808. (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1809. (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1810. (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1811. (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1812. (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1813. (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1814. (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1815. (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1816. (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1817. (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1818. (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1819. (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1820. (Box 146, Folder 36)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1821. (Box 146, Folder 37)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1822. (Box 146, Folder 38)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1823. (Box 146, Folder 39)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1824. (Box 146, Folder 40)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1825. (Box 146, Folder 41)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1826. (Box 146, Folder 42)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1827. (Box 146, Folder 43)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1828. (Box 146, Folder 44)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1829. (Box 146, Folder 45)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1830. (Box 146, Folder 46)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1831. (Box 146, Folder 47)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1832. (Box 146, Folder 48)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1833. (Box 146, Folder 49)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1834. (Box 146, Folder 50)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1835. (Box 146, Folder 51)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1836. (Box 146, Folder 52)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1837. (Box 146, Folder 53)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1838. (Box 146, Folder 54)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1839. (Box 146, Folder 55)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1840. (Box 146, Folder 56)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1841. (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1842. (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1843. (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1844. (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1845. (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1846. (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1847. (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1848. (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1849. (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1850. (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1851. (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1852. (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1853. (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1855. (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1856. (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Spotsylvania County, undated. (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Stafford County, 1785. (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Stafford County, 1786. (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Stafford County, 1787. (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Stafford County, 1788. (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Stafford County, 1790. (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Stafford County, 1794. (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Stafford County, 1795. (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Stafford County, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Stafford County, 1797. (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Stafford County, 1798. (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Stafford County, 1800. (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Stafford County, 1801. (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Stafford County, 1802. (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Stafford County, 1803. (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Stafford County, 1804. (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Stafford County, 1805. (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Stafford County, 1806. (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Stafford County, 1807. (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Stafford County, 1808. (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Stafford County, 1809. (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Stafford County, 1810. (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Stafford County, 1811. (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Stafford County, 1812. (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Stafford County, 1813. (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Stafford County, 1814. (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Stafford County, 1815. (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - Stafford County, 1816. (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - Stafford County, 1817. (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - Stafford County, 1818. (Box 148, Folder 29)
    - Stafford County, 1819. (Box 148, Folder 30)
    - Stafford County, 1821. (Box 148, Folder 31)
    - Stafford County, 1822. (Box 148, Folder 32)
    - Stafford County, 1823. (Box 148, Folder 33)
    - Stafford County, 1824. (Box 148, Folder 34)
    - Stafford County, 1825. (Box 148, Folder 35)
    - Stafford County, 1826. (Box 148, Folder 36)
    - Stafford County, 1827. (Box 148, Folder 37)
    - Stafford County, 1828. (Box 148, Folder 38)
    - Stafford County, 1829. (Box 148, Folder 39)
    - Stafford County, 1830. (Box 148, Folder 40)
    - Stafford County, 1831. (Box 148, Folder 41)
    - Stafford County, 1832. (Box 148, Folder 42)
    - Stafford County, 1833. (Box 148, Folder 43)
    - Stafford County, 1834. (Box 148, Folder 44)
    - Stafford County, 1836. (Box 148, Folder 45)
    - Stafford County, 1837. (Box 148, Folder 46)
    - Stafford County, 1838. (Box 148, Folder 47)
    - Stafford County, 1839. (Box 148, Folder 48)
    - Stafford County, 1840. (Box 148, Folder 49)
    - Stafford County, 1841. (Box 148, Folder 50)
    - Stafford County, 1842. (Box 148, Folder 51)
    - Stafford County, 1843. (Box 148, Folder 52)
    - Stafford County, 1844. (Box 148, Folder 53)
    - Stafford County, 1845. (Box 148, Folder 54)
    - Stafford County, 1846. (Box 148, Folder 55)
    - Stafford County, 1847. (Box 148, Folder 56)
    - Stafford County, 1848. (Box 148, Folder 57)
    - Stafford County, 1850. (Box 148, Folder 58)
    - Stafford County, 1851. (Box 148, Folder 59)
    - Stafford County, 1852. (Box 148, Folder 60)
    - Stafford County, 1853. (Box 148, Folder 61)
    - Stafford County, 1856. (Box 148, Folder 62)
    - Stafford County, undated. (Box 148, Folder 63)
    - Surry County, 1783. (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Surry County, 1785. (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Surry County, 1786. (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Surry County, 1787. (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Surry County, 1788. (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Surry County, 1789. (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Surry County, 1790. (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Surry County, 1791. (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Surry County, 1793. (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Surry County, 1794. (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Surry County, 1795. (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Surry County, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Surry County, 1797. (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Surry County, 1798. (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Surry County, 1799. (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Surry County, 1800. (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Surry County, 1801. (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Surry County, 1802. (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - Surry County, 1803. (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Surry County, 1804. (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Surry County, 1805. (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - Surry County, 1806. (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Surry County, 1807. (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Surry County, 1808. (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - Surry County, 1809. (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Surry County, 1810. (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - Surry County, 1811. (Box 149, Folder 27)
    - Surry County, 1812. (Box 149, Folder 28)
    - Surry County, 1813. (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - Surry County, 1814. (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - Surry County, 1815. (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Surry County, 1816. (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - Surry County, 1817. (Box 149, Folder 33)
    - Surry County, 1818. (Box 149, Folder 34)
    - Surry County, 1819. (Box 149, Folder 35)
    - Surry County, 1820. (Box 149, Folder 36)
    - Surry County, 1821. (Box 149, Folder 37)
    - Surry County, 1822. (Box 149, Folder 38)
    - Surry County, 1823. (Box 149, Folder 39)
    - Surry County, 1824. (Box 149, Folder 40)
    - Surry County, 1825. (Box 149, Folder 41)
    - Surry County, 1826. (Box 149, Folder 42)
    - Surry County, 1827. (Box 149, Folder 43)
    - Surry County, 1828. (Box 149, Folder 44)
    - Surry County, 1829. (Box 149, Folder 45)
    - Surry County, 1830. (Box 149, Folder 46)
    - Surry County, 1831. (Box 149, Folder 47)
    - Surry County, 1832. (Box 149, Folder 48)
    - Surry County, 1833. (Box 149, Folder 49)
    - Surry County, 1834. (Box 149, Folder 50)
    - Surry County, 1835. (Box 149, Folder 51)
    - Surry County, 1836. (Box 149, Folder 52)
    - Surry County, 1837. (Box 149, Folder 53)
    - Surry County, 1838. (Box 149, Folder 54)
    - Surry County, 1839. (Box 149, Folder 55)
    - Surry County, 1840. (Box 149, Folder 56)
    - Surry County, 1841. (Box 149, Folder 57)
    - Surry County, 1842. (Box 149, Folder 58)
    - Surry County, 1843. (Box 149, Folder 59)
    - Surry County, 1844. (Box 149, Folder 60)
    - Surry County, 1846. (Box 149, Folder 61)
    - Surry County, 1847. (Box 149, Folder 62)
    - Surry County, 1848. (Box 149, Folder 63)
    - Surry County, 1849. (Box 149, Folder 64)
    - Surry County, 1850. (Box 149, Folder 65)
    - Surry County, 1851. (Box 149, Folder 66)
    - Surry County, 1853. (Box 149, Folder 67)
    - Surry County, undated. (Box 149, Folder 68)
    - Sussex County, 1785. (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Sussex County, 1786. (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Sussex County, 1787. (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Sussex County, 1788. (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Sussex County, 1789. (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Sussex County, 1793. (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Sussex County, 1794. (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Sussex County, 1795. (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Sussex County, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Sussex County, 1797. (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Sussex County, 1798. (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Sussex County, 1799. (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Sussex County, 1800. (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Sussex County, 1801. (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Sussex County, 1803. (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Sussex County, 1804. (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Sussex County, 1805. (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Sussex County, 1806. (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Sussex County, 1807. (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Sussex County, 1808. (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Sussex County, 1809. (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Sussex County, 1810. (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Sussex County, 1811. (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Sussex County, 1812. (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Sussex County, 1813. (Box 150, Folder 25)
    - Sussex County, 1814. (Box 150, Folder 26)
    - Sussex County, 1815. (Box 150, Folder 27)
    - Sussex County, 1816. (Box 150, Folder 28)
    - Sussex County, 1817. (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - Sussex County, 1808. (Box 150, Folder 30)
    - Sussex County, 1819. (Box 150, Folder 31)
    - Sussex County, 1820. (Box 150, Folder 32)
    - Sussex County, 1821. (Box 150, Folder 33)
    - Sussex County, 1822. (Box 150, Folder 34)
    - Sussex County, 1823. (Box 150, Folder 35)
    - Sussex County, 1824. (Box 150, Folder 36)
    - Sussex County, 1825. (Box 150, Folder 37)
    - Sussex County, 1826. (Box 150, Folder 38)
    - Sussex County, 1827. (Box 150, Folder 39)
    - Sussex County, 1828. (Box 150, Folder 40)
    - Sussex County, 1829. (Box 150, Folder 41)
    - Sussex County, 1830. (Box 150, Folder 42)
    - Sussex County, 1831. (Box 150, Folder 43)
    - Sussex County, 1832. (Box 150, Folder 44)
    - Sussex County, 1833. (Box 150, Folder 45)
    - Sussex County, 1834. (Box 150, Folder 46)
    - Sussex County, 1835. (Box 150, Folder 47)
    - Sussex County, 1836. (Box 150, Folder 48)
    - Sussex County, 1837. (Box 150, Folder 49)
    - Sussex County, 1838. (Box 150, Folder 50)
    - Sussex County, 1839. (Box 150, Folder 51)
    - Sussex County, 1840. (Box 150, Folder 52)
    - Sussex County, 1841. (Box 150, Folder 53)
    - Sussex County, 1842. (Box 150, Folder 54)
    - Sussex County, 1843. (Box 150, Folder 55)
    - Sussex County, 1844. (Box 150, Folder 56)
    - Sussex County, 1845. (Box 150, Folder 57)
    - Sussex County, 1846. (Box 150, Folder 58)
    - Sussex County, 1847. (Box 150, Folder 59)
    - Sussex County, 1848. (Box 150, Folder 60)
    - Sussex County, 1849. (Box 150, Folder 61)
    - Sussex County, 1850. (Box 150, Folder 62)
    - Sussex County, 1851. (Box 150, Folder 63)
    - Sussex County, 1852. (Box 150, Folder 64)
    - Sussex County, 1853. (Box 150, Folder 65)
    - Sussex County, 1856. (Box 150, Folder 66)
    - Sussex County, undated. (Box 150, Folder 67)
    - Taylor County, 1845. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Taylor County, 1846. (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Taylor County, 1847. (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Taylor County, 1848. (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Taylor County, 1849. (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Taylor County, 1850. (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Taylor County, 1851. (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Taylor County, 1852. (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Taylor County, 1853. (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Taylor County, 1856. (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Tazewell County, 1800. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Tazewell County, 1801. (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Tazewell County, 1802. (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Tazewell County, 1803. (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Tazewell County, 1804. (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Tazewell County, 1805. (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Tazewell County, 1806. (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Tazewell County, 1807. (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Tazewell County, 1808. (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Tazewell County, 1809. (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Tazewell County, 1810. (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Tazewell County, 1811. (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Tazewell County, 1812. (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Tazewell County, 1813. (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Tazewell County, 1814. (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Tazewell County, 1816. (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Tazewell County, 1817. (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Tazewell County, 1818. (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Tazewell County, 1820. (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Tazewell County, 1821. (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Tazewell County, 1823. (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Tazewell County, 1824. (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - Tazewell County, 1825. (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - Tazewell County, 1826. (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - Tazewell County, 1827. (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - Tazewell County, 1828. (Box 152, Folder 26)
    - Tazewell County, 1829. (Box 152, Folder 27)
    - Tazewell County, 1831. (Box 152, Folder 28)